Finding aid for the Aldous and Laura Huxley papers, 1925-2007 LSC.2009
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Aldous Huxley Papers
  - Personal
    - Recordings
      - Laura Huxley, letter to Julian and Juliette Huxley, regarding last week of Aldous Huxley's life, Part II, 1963 Dec 1; UCLA Tape No. 209; Note on box: " L. letter to J & J, one track, Dec 1-63." [Tape 2] (Box 98, Folder 15)
      - Aldous Huxley and Laura Huxley, label on box reads, "Last day", 1963 Nov 16-17-18; UCLA Tape No. 211; Note on box: "3-3/4 speed, monophonic, 3rd gen., Nov. 16, 18, 18, 1963. Copy of orig 3/34/ half track roll #1, side #1 and side #2 almost to the end." Note and transcript of tape in box - not sent to recording studio. (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Aldous Huxley and Laura Huxley, talking days before his death, 1963 Nov 19; UCLA Tape No. 212; Note on box: "3-3/4 speed, monophonic, 3rd gen Tape 2, tail end of side #2 or roll #1 (16th-17th-18th-Nov. 1963) roll #2 (Nov. 19, 1963), sides # 1 and side #2 (but not to tail), de Biran, 2 discoveries, other [illegible]." Note and transcript in box - not sent to recording studio. (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Aldous Huxley reading aloud, Sermon in Cats, Poems from the Cicadas and the Dwarves from Chrome Yellow, no date; UCLA Tape No. 214 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Gerald Heard, Indications, Vedanta Press, 1975; UCLA Tape No. 228 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Gerald Heard, Reflections, Vedanta Press, 1975; UCLA Tape No. 229 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Meditations [?], holograph label reads "Health", no date; UCLA Tape No. 243 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Label reads: Aldous Letters Cristall; Aldous Huxley and Laura Huxley, dictation, personal correspondence, no date; UCLA Tape No. 398 (Box 115, Folder unknown container)
      - Label reads: S. Article A. and L. Nov. 20; Aldous Huxley and Laura Huxley reading and correcting article Shakespeare and Religion, 20 Nov 1963; UCLA Tape No. 388 (Box 115, Folder unknown container)
      - Label reads: Nov 21 About 100 feet L. reading S. Article Aldous correcting Last; Aldous Huxley and Laura Huxley working on "Shakespeare and Religion", 21 Nov 1963; UCLA Tape No. 387 (Box 115, Folder unknown container)
    - Research Related
      - Proceedings, Conference "The Creative Person," Institute of Personality Assesment and Research, University of California, Berkeley, Oct 1961 (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - Holograph note on Gerard Cordonnier, no date (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Sketch
      - Photocopy, lake [?] with mountains in background and bridge in foreground, no date (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Photocopy, lake surrounded by mountains, no date (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Photocopy, acupuncture drawings, no date (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Sketch of house with drawbridge, 4 copies, no date (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Sketch of house with hills in the background and foliage in the foreground, photocopy, no date (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Sketch of tree trunk and branches, photocopy, no date (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Photographs
    - Aldous Huxley age 8, no date; Photo ID No. 1; duplicates (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Aldous Huxley age 6-7, no date; Photo ID No. 2; duplicates (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Aldous Huxley with his Aunt, Mrs. Humprey Ward, no date; Photo ID No. 3 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Aldous Huxley as a child with his grandfather, Thomas Henry Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 4; not photo (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Aldous huxley as a child, profile, no date; Photo ID No. 5; not photo (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Aldous Huxley as a child, no date; Photo ID No. 6; not photo (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Aldous Huxley novelist, critic and poet, no date; Photo ID No. 7; not photo (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Aldous Huxley as a young man with glasses, 2-Aug-33; Photo ID No. 8; not photo, with text (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Aldous Huxley as a young man, A portrait accepted in place of one of Bernard Shaw: Aldous Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 9; not photo, clipping (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Aldous, Maria and Matthew Huxley in Forte olei Marmi, Italy, 1926?; Photo ID No. 10 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Aldous Huxley as a young man with glasses and hat, 1930; Photo ID No. 11; not photo, postcard (original photo by Dorothy Wilding (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Aldous Huxley as a young man with glasses, 3/4 angle, 1934; Photo ID No. 12; not photo, postcard (original photo by Howard Coster) (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Aldous Huxley in car in Bethelehem, PA, 1939; Photo ID No. 13; (original photo by Lou Stoumen) (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Maria Nys as a child with two unidentified boys, no date; Photo ID No. 14; postcard? (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Aldous Huxley with Matthew Huxley as infant, no date; Photo ID No. 15 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Maria Huxley with Matthew Huxley as child in London, no date; Photo ID No. 16 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Aldous and Maria Huxley with unidentified girl, no date; Photo ID No. 17 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Postcard from Aldous Huxley to Matthew Huxley with hand drawn images, 1924; Photo ID No. 18 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Postcard from Aldous Huxley to Matthew Huxley with image of a chimpanzee, 1924; Photo ID No. 19 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Aldous and Maria Huxley with unidentified woman, no date; Photo ID No. 20 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Aldous and Maria Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 21 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Aldous and Matthew Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 22 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Aldous and Maria Huxley with two unidentified individuals in front of house (1), no date; Photo ID No. 23 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Aldous and Maria Huxley with two unidentified individuals in front of house (2), no date; Photo ID No. 23 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Aldous Maria and Matthew Huxley with unidentified woman in front of house, no date; Photo ID No. 24 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Aldous Maria and Matthew Huxley with unidentified others in front of Christmas tree, no date; Photo ID No. 25 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Aldous and Maria Huxley in front of house, no date; Photo ID No. 26; duplicates (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Huxley house exterior Wrightwood CA, 1946-1949; Photo ID No. 27 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Huxley house interior, no date; Photo ID No. 28 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Aldous and Maria Huxley inside house on couch, no date; Photo ID No. 29 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Aldous and Maria Huxley with Swami Prabhavanda and two unidentified women, no date; Photo ID No. 30 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Aldous and Maria Huxley with Swami Prabhavanda and one unidentified woman, no date; Photo ID No. 31 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Aldous and Julian Huxley seated talking (1), no date; Photo ID No. 32 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Aldous and Julian Huxley seated talking (2), no date; Photo ID No. 33 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Aldous and Maria Huxley with Julian Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 34 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Aldous Huxley with grandchildren Trevenen and Tessa and Ellen Hovde (?), no date; Photo ID No. 35 (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Aldous Huxley with grandson Trevenen Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 36 (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Tessa Huxley portrait profile seated, no date; Photo ID No. 37; mounted on matting (original photograph by Barbara Sutro) (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Trevenen Huxley portrait close up, no date; Photo ID No. 38; mounted on matting (original photograph by Barbara Sutro) (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Trevenen Huxley at typewriter, no date; Photo ID No. 39 (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Trevenen Huxley with two unidentified boys, no date; Photo ID No. 40 (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Trevenen Huxley seated with cat, no date; Photo ID No. 41 (Box 65, Folder 41)
    - Matthew Huxley seated outside, no date; Photo ID No. 42 (Box 65, Folder 42)
    - Matthew Trevenen and Tessa Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 43 (Box 65, Folder 43)
    - Aldous with Matthew Treveven and Tessa Huxley with Judith Wallet Bordage and unidentified man, no date; Photo ID No. 44 (Box 65, Folder 44)
    - Matthew Huxley with Judith Wallet Bordage and unidentified man, no date; Photo ID No. 45 (Box 65, Folder 45)
    - Matthew Huxley with cigarette and unidentified man, no date; Photo ID No. 46 (Box 65, Folder 46)
    - Trevenen and Tessa Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 47 (Box 65, Folder 47)
    - Trevenen Huxley with unidentified others at gathering in a house, no date; Photo ID No. 48 (Box 65, Folder 48)
    - Judith Wallet Bordage with cat, no date; Photo ID No. 49 (Box 65, Folder 49)
    - Judith Wallet Bordage (1), no date; Photo ID No. 50 (Box 65, Folder 50)
    - Judith Wallet Bordage (2), no date; Photo ID No. 51 (Box 65, Folder 51)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley standing in front of tree, no date; Photo ID No. 52; (original photo by Wide World Photos) (Box 65, Folder 52)
    - Aldous Huxley with Laura Huxley holding a book; related photos added, no date; Photo ID No. 53; duplicates; added photos not yet digitized (Box 65, Folder 53)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley seated at table with unidenitified others, no date; Photo ID No. 54 (Box 65, Folder 54)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley seated with unidentified women, no date; Photo ID No. 55 (Box 65, Folder 55)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley walking wearing coats, no date; Photo ID No. 56 (Box 65, Folder 56)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley seated looking off to right, no date; Photo ID No. 57 (Box 65, Folder 57)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley both reclining, no date; Photo ID No. 58 (Box 65, Folder 58)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley with Princess Marie-Jose of Belgium and two unidentified others, 1961; Photo ID No. 59 (Box 65, Folder 59)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley at house after fire, no date; Photo ID No. 60 (Box 65, Folder 60)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley walking and talking, no date; Photo ID No. 61 (Box 65, Folder 61)
    - Aldous Huxley reclined and Laura Huxley (1), no date; Photo ID No. 62 (Box 65, Folder 62)
    - Aldous Huxley reclined and Laura Huxley (2), no date; Photo ID No. 62 (Box 65, Folder 62)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley both examining newspaper, no date; Photo ID No. 63 (Box 65, Folder 63)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley looking up at camera from newspaper, no date; Photo ID No. 64; CK and LH added "Aldous and Laura looking up at camera fro newspaper with unidentified children [LH's niece and nephew Piero]" to this folder (Box 65, Folder 64)
    - Laura Huxley standing next to short wall, no date; Photo ID No. 65 (Box 65, Folder 65)
    - Aldous Huxley in indigenous village in Brazil with three unidentified men, [1958]; Photo ID No. 67; corresponds with LH correspondence folder in series "Grey Metal Box" in this collection (Box 65, Folder 67)
    - Laura Huxley in indigenous village in Brazil with unidentified man, [1958]; Photo ID No. 67 (Box 65, Folder 67)
    - Aldous Huxley with Marie Le Put ?, no date; Photo ID No. 69; duplicates (Box 65, Folder 69)
    - Huxley house under Hollywood sign, no date; Photo ID No. 70 (Box 65, Folder 70)
    - Aldous and Maria Huxley bookplate design, no date; Photo ID No. 71 (Box 65, Folder 71)
    - Bust of Aldous Huxley (1), no date; Photo ID No. 72 (Box 65, Folder 72)
    - Jiddu Krishnamurti seated, no date; Photo ID No. 73; not photo (Box 65, Folder 73)
    - Jiddu Krishnamurti standing portrait, no date; Photo ID No. 73; not photo (Box 65, Folder 73)
    - Jiddu Krishnamurti portrait, no date; Photo ID No. 73 (Box 65, Folder 73)
    - Bust of Aldous Huxley (2), no date; Photo ID No. 74 (Box 65, Folder 74)
    - Drawn portrait of Aldous Huxley by Georges Schreiber, 1937; Photo ID No. 75 (Box 65, Folder 75)
    - Drawn portrait of Aldous Huxley by Don Bachardy (1), includes exhibit brochure, 1962; Photo ID No. 76 (Box 65, Folder 76)
    - Drawn portrait of Aldous Huxley by Don Bachardy (2), 1962; Photo ID No. 76 (Box 65, Folder 76)
    - Pamphlet of event titled The Human Potential at Rancho La Puerta, Tecate, CA, 1960; Photo ID No. 77; not photo (Box 65, Folder 77)
    - Clipping of image of Aldous Huxley from Italian periodical, no date; Photo ID No. 78; not photo (Box 65, Folder 78)
    - Clipping of image of Aldous Huxley speaking with Huston Smith from St. Louis Post, 19-Jan-58; Photo ID No. 79; not photo (Box 65, Folder 79)
    - Clipping of article titled Huxley Returns Wed. to Address Students from LA City College publication Nite News, 15-Apr; Photo ID No. 80; not photo (Box 65, Folder 80)
    - Clipping of article titled Huxley hos Blixen, Aug-61; Photo ID No. 81; not photo, scandanavian language? (Box 65, Folder 81)
    - Clipping of article titled Swami, Meet Garbo from Time Magazine, 13-Jan-97; Photo ID No. 82; not photo (Box 65, Folder 82)
    - Clipping of image of Laura Huxley receiving film interview of Aldous Huxley from USC professor Dr. Herman Harvey, 1-Jul-65; Photo ID No. 83; not photo (Box 65, Folder 83)
    - Clipping of article titled Morreu Aldous Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 84; not photo (Box 65, Folder 84)
    - Postcard of Yuma's Famous Drive-in Chapel, no date; Photo ID No. 85; not photo (Box 65, Folder 85)
    - Unidentified woman possibly related to Laura Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 86 (Box 65, Folder 86)
    - Unidentified boy wearing costume with drum, no date; Photo ID No. 87 (Box 65, Folder 87)
    - Unidentified boy wearing costume holding hands up, no date; Photo ID No. 87 (Box 65, Folder 87)
    - Unidentified man, no date; Photo ID No. 88 (Box 65, Folder 88)
    - Colosseum in Rome, no date; Photo ID No. 89 (Box 65, Folder 89)
    - Denmark, no date; Photo ID No. 90 (Box 65, Folder 90)
    - John Gielgud with two unidentified people, no date; Photo ID No. 91 (Box 65, Folder 91)
    - Laura Huxley with two unidentified people, no date; Photo ID No. 92 (Box 65, Folder 92)
    - Unidentified people seated together outside, no date; Photo ID No. 93 (Box 65, Folder 93)
    - Unidentified people inside house, no date; Photo ID No. 93 (Box 65, Folder 93)
    - Unidentified people in boat, no date; Photo ID No. 93 (Box 65, Folder 93)
    - Richar Baltus Dick 10 months, no date; Photo ID No. 94; possibly related to Maria Huxley? (Box 65, Folder 94)
    - Postcard from Laura Huxley to Margueritte Nys, no date; Photo ID No. 95; not photo (Box 65, Folder 95)
    - Four unidentified people in the desert, no date; Photo ID No. 96; mounted on paper (Box 65, Folder 96)
    - Three unidentified people in the desert, no date; Photo ID No. 97 (Box 65, Folder 97)
    - Card with photo inscribed greetings from Tinka and Robbie, no date; Photo ID No. 98 (Box 65, Folder 98)
    - Aldous Huxley gesturing with hands up looking down, no date; Reproduction from newspaper clipping (Box 65, Folder 99)
    - Aldous Huxley seated at a table with Gerald Heard and unidentified man, no date; Photo ID No. 99 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait in doorway, no date; Photo ID No. 100; original photo by Caskey (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait 3/4 arms crossed, no date; Photo ID No. 101; original photo by Blackstone-Shelburne New York (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait hand to chin in booklet titled L'Oeuvre, 1949; Photo ID No. 102; not photo (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Aldous Huxley seated hand to cheek reading, 1960; Photo ID No. 103 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Aldous Huxley outside holding coat walking talking with unidentified man, no date; Photo ID No. 104 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Aldous Huxley seated 3/4 hand to face arm on couch, no date; Photo ID No. 105; duplicates (original photo by George Kramer) (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Aldous Huxley seated profile hand to face eyes closed; other related photos, no date; Photo ID No. 106; duplicates; added photos not yet digitized (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Aldous Huxley at dinner party with Ginny Pfeiffer ?, 1958; Photo ID No. 107 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Aldous Huxley at Saltwood Castle, 1963; Photo ID No. 108 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Aldous Huxley in a crowd at UC Berkeley (2), no date; Photo ID No. 109 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Aldous Huxley in a crowd at UC Berkeley (3), no date; Photo ID No. 109 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Aldous Huxley in a crowd at UC Berkeley (1), no date; Photo ID No. 109 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Aldous Huxley with Paula [Kathy?] and Juan Pfeiffer, no date; Photo ID No. 110 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Aldous Huxley looking off to side outside with unidentified man and two unidentified children, no date; Photo ID No. 111; duplicates (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait profile seated on couch extended arm legs crossed, no date; Photo ID No. 112; original photo by Douglass Glass U.K. (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Aldous Huxley standing outside holding coat with unidentified man and woman (1), no date; Photo ID No. 113 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Aldous Huxley standing outside holding coat with unidentified man and woman (2), no date; Photo ID No. 113 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Aldous Huxley standing outside holding coat with unidentified woman (2), no date; Photo ID No. 113 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Aldous Huxley standing outside holding coat with unidentified woman (1), no date; Photo ID No. 113 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Aldous Huxley standing outside holding coat with unidentified man (2), no date; Photo ID No. 113 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Aldous Huxley standing outside holding coat with unidentified man (1), no date; Photo ID No. 113 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Aldous Huxley close up looking up, no date; Photo ID No. 114 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Aldous Huxley close up looking down talking, no date; Photo ID No. 115 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Aldous Huxley at podium at Dartmouth College Hanover, NH, 16-Sep-60; Photo ID No. 116 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Aldous Huxley seated at Dartmouth College Hanover NH, 8-10 Sept 1960; Photo ID No. 117 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Aldous Huxley with Indian Ambassador to the United States at Dartmouth College Hanover NH, 9-Sep-60; Photo ID No. 118 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Aldous Huxley with John Dickey at Dartmouth College Hanover NH, 8-10 Sept 1960; Photo ID No. 119 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Aldous Huxley with Dr. Norman Topping and George Cukor, no date; Photo ID No. 120 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Aldous Huxley with Dr. Norman Topping (3), no date; Photo ID No. 121 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Aldous Huxley with Dr. Norman Topping (1), no date; Photo ID No. 121 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Aldous Huxley with Dr. Norman Topping (2), no date; Photo ID No. 121 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Aldous Huxley with Dr. Raymond Kendall, no date; Photo ID No. 122 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Aldous Huxley close up 3/4 looking down talking, no date; Photo ID No. 123 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Aldous Huxley with Meira Penna and Antonio Callado with unidentified man, no date; Photo ID No. 124 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait profile looking down dark (1), no date; Photo ID No. 125; original photo by Phoenix Hamilton (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait profile looking down dark (2), no date; Photo ID No. 125; original photo by Phoenix Hamilton (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Aldous Huxley seated profile looking down, no date; Photo ID No. 126 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Aldous Huxley at podium, no date; Photo ID No. 127 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Aldous Huxley with unidentified man holding small statue award, no date; Photo ID No. 128 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Aldous Huxley at the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations Conference Rome Italy (1), 1963; Photo ID No. 129 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Aldous Huxley at the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations Conference Rome Italy (7), 1963; Photo ID No. 129 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Aldous Huxley at the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations Conference Rome Italy (6), 1963; Photo ID No. 129 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Aldous Huxley at the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations Conference Rome Italy (5), 1963; Photo ID No. 129 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Aldous Huxley at the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations Conference Rome Italy (4), 1963; Photo ID No. 129 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Aldous Huxley at the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations Conference Rome Italy (3), 1963; Photo ID No. 129 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Unidentified men at the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations Conference Rome Italy, 1963; Photo ID No. 129 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Aldous Huxley at the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations Conference Rome Italy (2), 1963; Photo ID No. 129 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - The Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations Conference Rome Italy, 1963; Photo ID No. 129 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - S.Y. Krishnaswamy and Dr. N. Wright with unidentified men at the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations Conference Rome Italy, 1963; Photo ID No. 129 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Aldous Huxley drafting outline for Potential of Man at WAAS meeting Stockholm Sweden (1), 1963; Photo ID No. 130 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Aldous Huxley drafting outline for Potential of Man at WAAS meeting Stockholm Sweden (5), 1963; Photo ID No. 130 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Aldous Huxley drafting outline for Potential of Man at WAAS meeting Stockholm Sweden (3), 1963; Photo ID No. 130 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Aldous Huxley drafting outline for Potential of Man at WAAS meeting Stockholm Sweden (7), 1963; Photo ID No. 130 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Aldous Huxley drafting outline for Potential of Man at WAAS meeting Stockholm Sweden (2), 1963; Photo ID No. 130 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Aldous Huxley drafting outline for Potential of Man at WAAS meeting Stockholm Sweden (6), 1963; Photo ID No. 130 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Aldous Huxley drafting outline for Potential of Man at WAAS meeting Stockholm Sweden (4), 1963; Photo ID No. 130 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Aldous Huxely with M. Sullivan at Presbyterian church Lake Forest Ill, 7-Apr-60; Photo ID No. 131 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Aldous Huxley speaking at event San Francisco State College Industrial Arts Department, no date; Photo ID No. 132 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Aldous Huxley close up smiling, no date; Photo ID No. 133 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Aldous Huxley 3/4 leaning on elbow hands clasped wearing scarf, no date; Photo ID No. 134; original photo by Jay Barrie Santa Monica CA (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Aldous Huxley seated 3/4 smiling holding a copy of Doors of Perception, no date; Photo ID No. 135; original photo by Jack Case Los Angeles CA ? (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Aldous Huxley seated looking down hands clasped, no date; Photo ID No. 136; original photo by Ralph Steiner (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Aldous Huxley with a bust of Benjamin Franklin, no date; Photo ID No. 137 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Aldous Huxley standing in snow in mountains, no date; Photo ID No. 138 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Aldous Huxley close up looking down smiling, no date; Photo ID No. 139 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait profile hand to forehead, no date; Photo ID No. 140; original photo by Douglass Glass U.K. (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - Aldous Huxley close up eyes closing, no date; Photo ID No. 141 (Box 66, Folder 43)
    - Aldous Huxley close up eyes closed, no date; Photo ID No. 142 (Box 66, Folder 44)
    - Aldous Huxley profile talking outside, no date; Photo ID No. 143; original photo by George Kramer (Box 66, Folder 45)
    - Aldous Huxley standing in grass, no date; Photo ID No. 144; cropped photo (Box 66, Folder 46)
    - Aldous Huxley close up hand to cheek, no date; Photo ID No. 145 (Box 66, Folder 47)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait in writing studio hand to cheek tweed blazer Llano CA, 1944; Photo ID No. 146; original photo signed Rose Nys Wessberg (Box 66, Folder 48)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait in writing studio 3/4 holding pen tweed blazer Llano CA, 1944; Photo ID No. 146; original photo signed Rose Nys Wessberg (Box 66, Folder 48)